

# eli FRAZIER

www.coderfoundry.com/elifrazier

HTML5 CSS3

FRAMEWORKS &

**PROGRAMMING** 

**LANGUAGES** 

JavaScript

JQuery

Bootstrap

.NET C#

MVC

ASP.NET

SQL

LINQ

Xamarin

WebAPI

## CODER FOUNDRY

1231 Shields Road, Suite 5 Kernersville, NC 27284 (336) 231-8632

partnerships@coderfoundry.com

This resume contains information furnished by the candidate and has not been independently verified by Coder Foundry, LLC.

This information is privileged, confidential, and to be used solely by the individual and entity to which it has been submitted.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **Coder Foundry, Web Software Engineer**

Kernersville, NC · August 2018-November 2018

- Created three projects, including:
  - A portfolio site using C#, MVC, HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP, JS & jQuery.
  - A Financial Portal implemented in three phases. Phase 1: an MVC Web Application, Phase 2: a Web Service that utilizes Swagger and Swashbuckle for integrated testing, Phase 3: A cross platform Xamarin Mobile Application
  - Fully designed and developed a multi-functional issue tracker web application, implementing enhanced roles & security, which also used a Code First Relational database designed and modeled in SQL Server. Technologies used include: .Net Framework v. 4.6.1, MVC6, C#, LINQ, SQL, Entity Framework, jQuery DataTables.

#### **Lexington Youth Theater, Volunteer**

Lexington, NC · September 2016–Present

• Volunteered as a builder and backstage hand for the Lexington Youth Theater, helping put together four productions.

#### **KFC, Team Member**

Lexington, NC · March 2011–October 2011

- Crosstrained in front and back of house and by managers admission was one of the top employees.
- Managed high school requirements while working 20 plus hours per week.

### **EDUCATION**

#### West Davidson High, High School Diploma

Lexington, NC · 2018